[organ music]
[管风琴音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[snoring]
[打鼾]
[alarm blaring]
[警报声]
[wolf howling]
[狼嚎]
- Pick me!
- Me!
- 选我吧！
- 我！
Pick me!
选我吧！
- Pick... pick Me!
- Me!
- 选择...选择我！
- 我！
all: Aw.
全体：噢。
[yawns]
[哈欠]
[hissing]
[嘶嘶声]
Ah, Esmeralda.
Good evening.
啊，埃斯梅拉达。
晚上好。
[spooky music]
[幽灵音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[clears throat]
[清嗓子]
Wakey-wakes, Master.
醒醒吧，主人。
The first blood of the day
is the most important.
今天的第一滴血
是最重要的。
Huh?
Master?
啊？
掌握？
[gasps]
[喘气]
[hisses]
[sneezes]
[嘶嘶声]
[打喷嚏]
[whimpers]
[呜咽]
Oh, no.
哦，不。
You've got a stuffy Nose-feratu.
你的鼻子不通气。
[sneezes]
[打喷嚏]
[hisses]
[嘶嘶声]
[sneezes]
[打喷嚏]
[whimpers]
[呜咽]
We have to get you
to Dr. Calamari right away.
我们必须找到你
立即联系 Calamari 博士。
[eerie music]
[怪异音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[breathing heavily]
[呼吸粗重]
[sneezes]
[打喷嚏]
[groans]
[呻吟]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[sneezes]
[打喷嚏]
Next patient.
下一个病人。
Salutations, Dr. Calamari.
问候，卡拉马里博士。
The master has a case of
the Transylvanian sniff-sniffs.
大师有一个案例
特兰西瓦尼亚的嗅嗅。
Can you help?
你能帮忙吗？
[screeches]
[尖叫声]
Thank you
for bringing him in, Slappy.
谢谢你
把他带进来，斯拉皮。
I'll steam those allergies
right out of his schnoz.
我会消除那些过敏
就在他的鼻子里。
[screeches]
[尖叫声]
Come back in two hours
und pick him up.
两小时后回来
并接他。
I'll be right back, Master.
我马上就回来，主人。
Oh, I almost forgot.
哦，我差点忘了。
[laughs]
[笑]
[sneezes]
[打喷嚏]
[growls]
[咆哮]
Yes, Master.
是的，师父。
I will bring you blood samples
und cookies.
我会给你带来血样
和饼干。
Two hours?
两个小时？
What am I gonna do
for two whole hours?
我要做什么
整整两个小时？
Let's find out, eh?
Eh?
让我们来了解一下，嗯？
呃？
♪ ♪
♪♪
[electronic music]
[电子音乐]
Get ready to prance, prance
on your grave!
准备好腾跃吧，腾跃吧
在你的坟墓上！
Oh, I just love to prance.
哦，我只是喜欢跳跃。
♪ ♪
♪♪
Oh, I feel so free and loose!
哦，我感到如此自由和放松！
♪ ♪
♪♪
[buzzer blares]
[蜂鸣器鸣响]
Hooray!
I made a swish.
万岁！
我“嗖”地一声。
[all cheering]
[大家欢呼]
Step right up
and squirt yourself a prize!
向右走一步
并给自己喷一个奖品！
[laughs]
Yeah!
[笑]
是啊！
Ooh!
哦！
We have a winner!
我们有赢家了！
Winner, winner!
赢家，赢家！
Step right up
and squirt yourself a prize!
向右走一步
并给自己喷一个奖品！
Oh!
Reach for the sky, bottles.
哦！
伸手向天空，瓶子。
Whoa!
Ah! Oh!
哇！
啊!哦！
Step right up, and squ...
直接站起来，然后...
[explosion]
[爆炸]
[all cheer]
[大家欢呼]
We have another winner.
我们还有另一个赢家。
[laughs]
Uh-oh.
[笑]
呃哦。
[tires screeching]
[轮胎的尖叫声]
[loud thud]
[巨响]
Oh, hello, Slippy.
噢，你好，滑溜。
You look positively disgusting
this evening.
你看起来确实很恶心
今天晚上。
[wheezing laugh]
[喘息笑声]
You look pretty horrifying
yourself, Slappy.
你看起来很可怕
你自己，斯拉皮。
[laughs]
[笑]
[laughter]
[笑声]
What can I get you today?
今天我能给你什么？
Oh, I need a can of bat food
哦，我需要一罐蝙蝠食物
and a flea collar
for the master.
和一个除蚤项圈
为了主人。
Oh, that master sure is lucky
呵呵，这位主人真是幸运啊
to have you looking out for him.
让你照顾他。
Oh.
[chuckles]
哦。
[笑声]
What do I owe you, gruesome?
我欠你什么，可恶？
Shh.
嘘。
It's on the house, stink lips.
就在房子里，嘴唇很臭。
Until our eyes
cross again, mon cheri.
直到我们的眼前
再次穿越，mon cheri。
[romantic music]
[浪漫音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
[record scratches]
[记录划痕]
Excuse me.
Do you sell snail diapers?
打扰一下。
有卖蜗牛尿布的吗？
- [meows]
- Ew.
- [喵]
- 呃。
Ah, it is always great to go
啊，去总是很棒的
on a picnic with old friends.
和老朋友去野餐。
Oh, Mr. Ribeye?
哦，肋眼先生？
Mr. Ribeye,
do you have the time?
肋眼先生，
你有时间吗？
Oh, I have to pick up
the master.
哦，我得去接
主人。
See you soon, everyone,
but hopefully not too soon.
大家好久不见
但希望不会太快。
[laughs]
[笑]
- Bye!
- 再见！
- See you later, Slappy!
- See you!
- 再见，斯拉皮！
- 再见！
Come back soon!
快回来吧！
- Nosferatu.
- 诺斯费拉图。
Dr. Calamari, I'm back.
卡拉马里博士，我回来了。
Nosferatu.
诺斯费拉图。
So tell me, Doctor,
is the master cured?
所以告诉我，医生，
主人痊愈了吗？
All better!
一切都好起来了！
Make sure he takes these
nose drops twice a night.
确保他拿走这些
每晚滴两次鼻涕。
Oh, thank you, Dr. C.
哦，谢谢你，C 博士。
Who was a good vampire?
谁是一个善良的吸血鬼？
Hmm?
唔？
[slurping]
[发出声音]
[chuckles]
[笑声]
[upbeat music]
[欢快的音乐]
♪ ♪
♪♪
Oh, yes, of course I bought you
哦，是的，我当然买了你
that flea collar
you saw in the window.
那个跳蚤项圈
你在窗户里看到的。
[laughs]
[笑]
Very fetching, Master.
太有魅力了，师父。
Huh?
啊？
I'll put that
in the fridge for later.
我会把那个
放在冰箱里待会儿用。
[grumbles]
[抱怨]
Oh, you don't have
to thank me, Master.
哦，你没有
来感谢我，师父。
You're my best friend.
[laughs]
你是我最好的朋友。
[笑]
Oh!
哦！
Yes, Master!
Let's go home now.
是的，师父！
我们现在回家吧。
♪ ♪
♪♪
First one to the castle
第一个到城堡的
is a filthy, stinking cesspool
of despair!
是一个又脏又臭的污水池
绝望！
♪ ♪
♪♪
Huh?
啊？
I am soaring like a bat!
Soaring!
我像蝙蝠一样翱翔！
飙升！
Oh!
哦！